[
    {
        "question": "In a popular children's song, how do \"the wheels on the bus\" go?",
        "answers": [
            "Against the grain",
            "For broke",
            "Round and round"
        ],
        "questionNumber": 1,
        "time": 1534640674.2195075,
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What farm animal is categorized as poultry?",
        "answers": [
            "Bull",
            "Chicken",
            "Pig"
        ],
        "questionNumber": 2,
        "time": 1534640707.1562788,
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these units measures the intensity of sound?",
        "answers": [
            "Decibel",
            "Ampere",
            "Kelvin"
        ],
        "questionNumber": 3,
        "time": 1534640754.95089,
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these cities is known for flower arranging?",
        "answers": [
            "Buenos Aires",
            "Kyoto",
            "Milan"
        ],
        "questionNumber": 4,
        "time": 1534640796.443782,
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "In the original \"Donkey Kong,\" which is NOT a way the mustachioed hero can perish?",
        "answers": [
            "Timer runs out",
            "Life bar hits zero",
            "Falling"
        ],
        "questionNumber": 5,
        "time": 1534640830.327315,
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The tallest known peak in our solar system is on what planet?",
        "answers": [
            "Jupiter",
            "Mars",
            "Earth"
        ],
        "questionNumber": 6,
        "time": 1534640867.6392877,
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What legal chess move involves moving a pawn diagonally to an unoccupied square?",
        "answers": [
            "Fianchetto",
            "En passant",
            "Castling"
        ],
        "questionNumber": 7,
        "time": 1534640911.0483556,
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is a subtitle of a Michael Bay \"Transformers\" film?",
        "answers": [
            "Dark Side of the Moon",
            "Dark Moon",
            "Dark of the Moon"
        ],
        "questionNumber": 8,
        "time": 1534640958.570092,
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What animal has the largest eyes in the animal kingdom?",
        "answers": [
            "Giant Pacific octopus",
            "Giant squid",
            "Blue whale"
        ],
        "questionNumber": 9,
        "time": 1534640999.2183766,
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these hit singles is by the first band to play on every continent within a year?",
        "answers": [
            "Gimme Shelter",
            "Ants Marching",
            "Enter Sandman"
        ],
        "questionNumber": 10,
        "time": 1534641043.485441,
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "In grammar, which of these is NOT considered a coordinating conjunction?",
        "answers": [
            "As",
            "So",
            "For"
        ],
        "questionNumber": 11,
        "time": 1534641082.1230056,
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What special request did Muhammad Ali make for his star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame?",
        "answers": [
            "It couldn't be walked on",
            "Different color",
            "Larger size"
        ],
        "questionNumber": 12,
        "time": 1534641144.5924435,
        "answer": 1
    }
]
